>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们理解原型，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We understand prototypes,
我们知道它们上面的句法糖分是阶级制度
we understand the syntactic sugar on
top of them which is the class system.
但让我们再看看使用这个原型系统的另一种方式，我相信
But let's look at another way of using
this prototype system, which I believe
将在 JavaScript 中发现更多潜在的未来探索。
will uncover more potential future
exploration within JavaScript.
我相信我们还有更多的事情可以完成
I believe there's more things
that we can accomplish, and
我觉得我们可以更简单的做
I think we can do it in a simpler way.
所以我想让我们简化
So I want us to simplify.
我的风格与我们使用物体的方式不同
I have a different style of approaching
the way we use objects, and
他们之间的原型语言
the prototype language between them and
我将这种编码称为 OLOO，链接到其他对象的对象。
I call this style of coding OLOO,
Objects Linked to Other Objects.
我需要一些与 OO 和 OO 形成鲜明对比的术语
I needed some kind of catchy
term to contrast with OO and
可悲的现实是，面向对象实际上是最好的术语。
the sad reality is that object
oriented is actually the best term.
你想想班上的语言
If you think about it,
class oriented languages
不应该被称为面向对象的语言。
should never have really called
themselves object oriented languages.
他们应该把自己称为阶级式。
They should have called
themselves class oriented.
但他们拿走了那个面向对象的怪物现在它卡住了
But they took on that object oriented
moniker, and now it's stuck and
我们不能重新定位目标的意义
we can't re-purpose
the meaning of object oriented.
但如果你真的认为存在两种语言
But if you really think about it
there are two languages in existence,
JavaScript 是其中一个， OLOO 是另一个。
JavaScript being one of them,
OLOO being the other.
我的知识有两种语言
Two languages in existence to my knowledge
其中，您可以在没有任何类的情况下创建对象。
where in you can create
an object without any class.
所以当你真正想的时候，只有两种真正面向对象的语言
So when you really think about it, the
only two truly object oriented languages
是 OLOO 和 JavaScript。
are OLOO and JavaScript.
但那艘船已经航行了
But that ship has sailed.
我们不能使用 OO，所以我们将它称为 OLOO，链接到其他对象的对象。
We can't use OO, so let's call it OLOO,
Objects Linked to Other Objects.
这就是有商标的
And that is trademarked,
所以如果你想用的话你得给我很多钱
so you need to pay me lots of
money if you want to use it.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
让我们来看看 OLOO 如何处理事情。
So let's look at how
OLOO approaches things.
请记住类语法。
Remember the class syntax.
这就是我们之前说过的
This is what we talked
about a little bit before.
类是一种图样化的方法
Classes are a way of patterning
不同实体之间的某种关系，并将其实例化。
some relationship between different
entities and instantiating them.
但在封面下记住
But under the covers, remember,
那个课实际上是在暗示这个枪支的权利吗
that that class is actually
implying all of this gunk right?
它实际上是在暗示所有这些原始类型。
It's actually implying
all of these prototypes.
所以如果我们能做一个编码方式来完成同样的事情
So what if we could do a style of coding
that accomplishes the same thing but
没有任何思考或设计课程的包袱
without any of the baggage of thinking or
designing with classes,
需要担心原型，或者超级，或者任何其他的东西，以及
needing to worry about prototypes, or
super, or any of that other stuff, and
肯定不需要再使用新的关键词了
certainly never needing to
use the new key word again.
如果我们能让对象链接到其他对象呢 ?
What if we could just make
objects link to other objects?
以下是该代码的 OLOO 样式表示。
Here's the OLOO style
representation of that code.
我要你在这里看到的是我现在只有东西了
What I want you to see here is
that I have only objects now.
讲习班不是一项职能。
Workshop is not a function.
这不是一类人
It's not a class.
这只是个物体
It's just an object.
AnotherWorkshop 只是一个对象。
AnotherWorkshop is just an object.
我正在通过 Object.create 链接它，但它只是一个对象。
I am linking it via Object.create
the workshop but it is just an object.
JJSRecentParts 只是链接到另一个研讨会的对象。
And the JSRecentParts is just an object
that is linked to another workshop.
所以当我打电话给JSRecentPart.sett师资时，它没有那个方法，但是它
So when I call JSRecentPart.setteacher,
it doesn't have that method but it
再去另一个没有这个办法的车间，但是去了这个车间。
goes to another workshop who doesn't have
that method, but it goes to this workshop.
然后发现老师，用这个电话的装订
And then it finds set teacher, and
it uses this binding of the call site
在 JSRecentPart上设置属性。
to set a property on JSRecentPart's.
所以我们从阶级制度中得到了同样的好处。
So we're getting the same
benefits of a class system.
但是注意现在缺少的东西。
But notice what is missing now.
我们没有更多的样机我们没有更多的构造函数
We don't have any more .prototypes, we
don't have any more constructor functions,
我们又没有新的关键词了
and we don't have any more new keywords.
我们只拥有与其他物体相连的物体
We just have objects
linked to other objects,
这里的魔术是我们用这个小东西叫
and the magic trick here is that
we use this little thing called
object.create 以创建和链接我们的对象。
object.create to make and
link our objects.
所以，物化，我显然没有发明。
So object.create,
I obviously didn't invent that.
在 ES5语言中添加了该语言。
That was added to
the language back in ES5.
这实际上是我们的好友道格 - 克罗克福德提议的。
That was actually proposed for JavaScript
by our good friend Doug Crockford.
他想出了 " 物化 " 的概念
He came up with the idea for
object.create and
他把它推到了委员会里然后加到了 ES5
he got it pushed through the committee and
added to ES5.
好主意道格
Great idea Doug.
太棒了
Fantastic.
这是我在 JavaScript中最喜欢的功能之一。
This is one of my favorite
features in JavaScript.
道格 - 克罗克福德 ( Doug Crockford ) 从没有拥有的对象创造和
As a little sad side note, Doug Crockford
has since disowned object.create and
不再认为我们应该用它来让我流泪
no longer thinks that we should use it at
all, which makes me a cry a little tear.
我喜欢这个功能因为我喜欢做物体
I love this feature because I love
being able to make objects and
把它们联系在一起而没有任何新的胡扯
link them together without any
of the nonsense of new, and
原始类型，构造函数和类，以及扩展，以及所有其他内容。
prototypes, and constructors, and classes,
and extends, and all of that other stuff.
我喜欢能充分利用物体的优势
I love just being able to take full
advantage of the objects oriented
在 JavaScript 中使用。
system in JavaScript.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不仅认为这是一个简单的风格
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Not only do I argue
that this is a simpler style and
如果按行比较，基本的语法非常小
if you looked line by line comparison,
there is essentially very little syntactic
此值与类等效值之间的差异。
difference between this and
the class equivalent.
这并不是等同的等级等同更多的含糖或其他东西。
It's not that class equivalent is just
massively more sugary or something.
它们本质上是非常接近等价的。
They're essentially very
close in equivalence.
但是这个直接暴露给你的地方
But where this one is exposing
to you directly instead
假装有一件事是不重要的
of pretending with an artifice
that it's something that it's not,
它直接暴露给你这些只是与其他物体相连的物体
it's exposing to you directly, these
are just objects linked to other objects.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在，物化如何创造魔法?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now,
how does object.create do that magic?
这是一个旧的填充对象，用于 object.create。
Well this is an old polyfill for
object.create.
我们不需要多填充预 ES5 的填充。
We don't need polyfills mostly for
pre-ES5 anymore.
但这是针对对象的 ES5 预填充。
But this was the pre-ES5 polyfill for
object.create.
看看它的作用，它是否真的起到了一个空虚的作用。
And look at what it does,
is it literally makes an empty function.
我们甚至都不关心它的功能
Cuz we don't even care
what the function is.
它将它的雏形设置为 " O " 的雏形
It sets its prototype to sum O,
and it calls new on
谁管什么功能给我们新创建的对象。
that who cares whatever function to
give us the newly created object.
换句话说，物化的方式创造了 OLOO的魔力
So, in other words, the way
object.create does the magic of OLOO,
我们把所有没人在乎的构造函数都带走
is we take all of those constructor
functions that nobody cares about and
所有没有人想写的样机
all those .prototypes that
nobody wants to write, and
所有这些都是混乱的新关键词
all those new keywords
that are just confusing.
我们把他们藏在物化的内部
And we hide them inside of object.create,
okay,
在我们的代码中只留下一个干净简单的物体之间的联系
leaving in our code just this clean,
simple linkage between objects.